<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MasterHttpRelayVPN-Frankestein</string>

    <!-- Top-bar -->
    <string name="tb_tagline">Relay client · local proxy &amp; optional VPN</string>
    <string name="tb_check_update_checking">checking…</string>
    <string name="tb_version_prefix">v</string>

    <!-- Welcome + section hints -->
    <string name="screen_intro_welcome">You are in the right place to route device traffic through your own Google Apps Script relay—with optional VPN (TUN) or proxy-only mode. Take two minutes to read the hints under each heading: they explain what to tap first, what each field does, and what to try when something fails.</string>
    <string name="field_mode">Mode</string>
    <string name="help_section_mode">Choose how traffic leaves this phone. Apps Script (MITM) is the full experience with HTTPS inspection. Google-only helps you reach script.google.com before you have a relay. Full tunnel needs your tunnel node but skips the user certificate flow.</string>
    <string name="help_section_relay">Paste the same deployment URLs (or bare IDs) and auth_key you configured in Apps Script. Multiple IDs spread load—especially important in full-tunnel mode. Leave this disabled when Mode is Google-only.</string>
    <string name="help_section_network">google_ip is the Google edge IPv4 you dial; front_domain is the hostname used in the outer TLS name. Wrong pairs cause timeouts—use Auto-detect, then the SNI tester, before assuming the relay is broken.</string>
    <string name="help_google_ip">Google frontend IPv4 that accepts TLS with your front_domain as SNI. If pages never load, revisit this value first.</string>
    <string name="help_front_domain">Hostname for the TLS Server Name Indication (not an IP). www.google.com is the usual starting point; your network may prefer another Google hostname.</string>
    <string name="help_before_connect">Connect saves your fields, starts the engine, and (in VPN mode) asks Android for permission. If Connect stays disabled, check that deployment URLs and auth_key are filled—or switch to Google-only while bootstrapping.</string>
    <string name="help_mode_overview">VPN mode routes eligible apps automatically. Proxy-only leaves the system VPN off: after connecting you must point Wi‑Fi or individual apps at the HTTP/SOCKS ports shown in the connection help text.</string>

    <!-- Section headers -->
    <string name="sec_apps_script_relay">Apps Script relay</string>
    <string name="sec_network">Network</string>
    <string name="sec_sni_pool_tester">SNI pool + tester</string>
    <string name="sec_advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="sec_live_logs">Live logs</string>
    <string name="sec_how_to_use">Help &amp; walkthrough</string>
    <string name="sec_app_splitting">App splitting</string>

    <!-- Primary actions -->
    <string name="btn_connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="btn_disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="btn_install_mitm">Install MITM certificate</string>
    <string name="btn_auto_detect_google_ip">Auto-detect google_ip</string>
    <string name="btn_test_all">Test all</string>
    <string name="btn_test">Test</string>
    <string name="btn_add">Add</string>
    <string name="btn_clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="btn_install">Install</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <!-- VPN / notification (used from MhrvVpnService) -->
    <string name="notif_channel_name">MasterHttpRelayVPN-Frankestein</string>
    <string name="notif_channel_desc">Foreground status while the relay tunnel is up</string>
    <string name="notif_vpn_title">VPN tunnel active</string>
    <string name="notif_vpn_text">Routing via SOCKS5 127.0.0.1:%1$d</string>
    <string name="notif_action_stop">Stop</string>

    <!-- Field labels -->
    <string name="field_deployment_urls">Deployment URL(s) or script ID(s)</string>
    <string name="field_auth_key">auth_key</string>
    <string name="field_google_ip">google_ip</string>
    <string name="field_front_domain">front_domain</string>
    <string name="field_connection_mode">Connection mode</string>
    <string name="field_add_custom_sni">Add custom SNI</string>

    <!-- Connection mode -->
    <string name="mode_vpn_tun">VPN (TUN) — routes every app</string>
    <string name="mode_proxy_only">Proxy only — configure per-app</string>

    <!-- App splitting -->
    <string name="split_all">All apps</string>
    <string name="split_only">Only selected apps</string>
    <string name="split_except">All except selected</string>
    <string name="split_pick_apps">Pick apps…</string>

    <!-- Install dialog title -->
    <string name="dialog_install_mitm_title">Install MITM certificate?</string>
    <string name="dialog_install_mitm_intro">MasterHttpRelayVPN-Frankestein uses a local certificate authority (CA) so it can inspect HTTPS, send bytes through your Apps Script relay, then encrypt them again toward real websites. Until you trust this CA in Android settings, browsers and apps will show certificate errors—that is expected.</string>
    <string name="dialog_install_mitm_steps">On Android 11 and newer there is no in-app install button for user CAs. When you tap Install we save a PEM file (Downloads/mhrv-ca.crt) and open Settings.\n\nIn Settings, use the search bar and open “CA certificate” (not “VPN &amp; app user certificate” or “Wi‑Fi certificate”). Pick the file from Downloads and confirm. If you do not use a screen lock, Android will ask you to add one first—this is an OS requirement for any user CA.</string>
    <string name="dialog_install_mitm_no_cert">The CA file is not ready yet. Tap Connect once so the engine can generate it, then open this dialog again.</string>

    <!-- Language toggle -->
    <string name="lang_toggle_cd">Switch language</string>

    <!-- Supporting / helper text -->
    <string name="help_deployment_urls">Use a full https://script.google.com/macros/s/…/exec URL or the bare deployment ID from the Apps Script editor. Add several IDs (one per row) to rotate traffic—more IDs mean more parallel capacity in full-tunnel mode. Each ID must belong to the same auth_key you paste below (per Google account, use separate groups in advanced desktop configs).</string>
    <string name="help_auth_key">Must match the AUTH_KEY constant inside Code.gs. If it is wrong, every relay call fails immediately—double-check for trailing spaces when copying.</string>
    <string name="help_mode_vpn_tun">Turns on Android’s VPN permission so traffic can be routed without per-app proxy settings. Banking and chat apps may still refuse HTTPS unless they trust your user CA—see the Help walkthrough for details.</string>
    <string name="help_mode_proxy_only">No system VPN. After you tap Connect, open Wi‑Fi advanced settings (or each app’s proxy options) and enter HTTP 127.0.0.1:%1$d and SOCKS5 127.0.0.1:%2$d. Only apps that respect those settings will use the tunnel.</string>
    <string name="help_sni_pool">Each enabled hostname is tried in rotation when opening TLS to google_ip. Run Test all before relying on the tunnel—if every line fails, your google_ip or DNS is usually wrong. Clearing everything lets the Rust engine fall back to its built-in Google list.</string>
    <string name="help_app_splitting">Pick whether every app, only selected apps, or all-but-selected apps should ride the VPN. This app always excludes itself so it can talk to the relay without looping. ONLY mode needs at least one other installable app; otherwise Android falls back to routing everyone.</string>

    <!-- SNI pool extras -->
    <string name="sni_selected_count">%1$d app(s) selected</string>

    <!-- Advanced section -->
    <string name="adv_verify_tls">Verify upstream TLS</string>
    <string name="adv_verify_tls_help">Keep this on in production. Turning it off skips TLS validation to Google’s edge—useful only while you diagnose handshake issues.</string>
    <string name="adv_log_level">log_level</string>
    <string name="adv_parallel_relay">parallel_relay: %1$d</string>
    <string name="adv_parallel_relay_help">How many duplicate relay attempts to launch per logical request. 1 is normal; raise cautiously on flaky networks because higher values burn Apps Script quota faster.</string>
    <string name="adv_upstream_socks5">upstream_socks5 (optional)</string>
    <string name="adv_upstream_socks5_help">Optional chain through another SOCKS5 (for example a local xray inbound). Leave empty for a direct hop to Google.</string>

    <!-- Live logs -->
    <string name="logs_lines_count">%1$d lines</string>

    <!-- Snackbar -->
    <string name="snack_google_ip_updated">google_ip updated to %1$s</string>
    <string name="snack_google_ip_current">google_ip already current (%1$s)</string>
    <string name="snack_dns_lookup_failed">DNS lookup failed — check network</string>

    <!-- Snackbar / status (HomeScreen) -->
    <string name="snack_update_available">Update available: v%1$s → v%2$s  %3$s</string>
    <string name="snack_cert_installed">Certificate installed ✓</string>
    <string name="snack_cert_not_installed">Certificate not yet installed.</string>
    <string name="snack_cert_saved_to">Saved to %1$s.</string>
    <string name="snack_cert_settings_hint">In Settings, search for “CA certificate” and install from there — NOT “VPN &amp; app user certificate” or “Wi‑Fi”.</string>
    <string name="snack_cert_tap_install_again">Tap Install again to retry.</string>

    <!-- Update check summary -->
    <string name="update_check_failed_no_response">Update check failed (no response)</string>
    <string name="update_check_up_to_date">Up to date (running v%1$s)</string>
    <string name="update_check_offline">Offline: %1$s</string>
    <string name="update_check_error">Check failed: %1$s</string>
    <string name="update_check_failed_unknown_response">Check failed (unknown response)</string>
    <string name="update_check_failed_bad_json">Check failed (bad json)</string>

    <!-- In-app guide — section titles + bodies -->
    <string name="guide_title_overview">What MasterHttpRelayVPN-Frankestein does</string>
    <string name="guide_body_overview">This app runs the same Rust engine as the desktop build. It opens HTTPS on your phone, sends traffic through your own Google Apps Script deployment using TLS domain fronting (your ISP usually sees a normal Google connection), then encrypts it again toward the real site. You need: a deployed script, the same auth_key in the app, and the user CA installed so Android trusts the local MITM.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_first_run">First-run checklist</string>
    <string name="guide_body_first_run">1) Deploy Code.gs from the project assets in script.google.com and publish as a Web app.\n2) Paste one or more deployment URLs (or bare IDs) and the auth_key here.\n3) Install the MITM certificate using the button below when the app offers it.\n4) Run the SNI tester; fix google_ip or front_domain if every probe fails.\n5) Choose VPN (TUN) or Proxy-only, then Connect.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_relay">Apps Script relay</string>
    <string name="guide_body_relay">Use full https://script.google.com/.../exec URLs or bare deployment IDs. Several IDs are rotated for higher throughput in full-tunnel mode. auth_key must match the constant inside your script. If you are unsure which Google edge IP works on your network, tap Auto-detect google_ip or try values from the desktop `mhrv-f scan-ips` tool.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_certificate">MITM certificate (HTTPS)</string>
    <string name="guide_body_certificate">Tap Install MITM certificate. We export Downloads/mhrv-ca.crt and jump to Settings. Search for “CA certificate”, pick the file from Downloads, and confirm—not the VPN user certificate flow. Android 11+ requires a screen lock before installing any user CA.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_sni">SNI pool + tester</string>
    <string name="guide_body_sni">Expand SNI pool + tester and run Test all before you rely on the tunnel. If every line fails, your google_ip may be wrong, poisoned by DNS, or blocked—try another Google frontend IP and keep front_domain as a hostname that answers on your network (often www.google.com).</string>
    <string name="guide_title_vpn_flow">Connect (VPN / TUN)</string>
    <string name="guide_body_vpn_flow">After fields look correct, tap Connect and approve the Android VPN prompt. A local HTTP and SOCKS listener starts together with TUN routing; eligible apps use the tunnel automatically without per-app proxy settings.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_app_split">App splitting</string>
    <string name="guide_body_app_split">In VPN mode you can send All apps, Only selected apps, or All except selected through the tunnel. This package always excludes itself so management traffic does not loop. If “Only selected” would be empty, the service falls back to All with self-exclusion.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_proxy_only">Proxy-only mode</string>
    <string name="guide_body_proxy_only">No system VPN. After Connect, set Wi‑Fi advanced proxy or per-app settings to HTTP 127.0.0.1:%1$d and SOCKS5 127.0.0.1:%2$d. Only apps that honour those settings are tunnelled.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_troubleshoot">Troubleshooting</string>
    <string name="guide_body_troubleshoot">504 / relay timeout — Apps Script quotas, slow script, or blocking; redeploy or add deployments. YouTube buffering/stutter often means too many googlevideo chunks are burning call count—add more deployments/accounts or lower fan-out. Certificate errors — reinstall the user CA from this screen. Odd hangs — re-check google_ip, front_domain, and URLs. Watch Live logs; on desktop use `mhrv-f doctor` for the same checks.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_turnstile">Cloudflare Turnstile</string>
    <string name="guide_body_turnstile">Sites that challenge every navigation may loop: relay traffic can leave from different Google IPs and carries a fixed Apps Script user-agent, so short-lived cookies may not stick. That is a property of relaying through Apps Script, not a defect in this client.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_docs">Downloads &amp; source</string>
    <string name="guide_body_docs">Official APKs and desktop builds are published on GitHub: https://github.com/AmirrezaFarnamTaheri/MasterHttpRelayVPN-Frankestein/releases — use that page if you need a fresh install or release notes.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_limits">HTTPS in other apps (read this)</string>
    <string name="guide_body_limits">Android 7+ lets each app opt out of user-installed certificate authorities. Browsers and many developer tools opt in; banking, streaming, and chat apps often do not. Those apps may still ride the VPN socket but will show certificate errors—that is expected MITM behavior, not a bug in this client. Use proxy-only mode or split tunneling when you only need specific apps.</string>
    <string name="guide_title_updates">Updates &amp; version</string>
    <string name="guide_body_updates">Tap the version chip in the top bar to check GitHub Releases. If the check fails on cellular Wi‑Fi, try again on a different network—the public API rate-limits some carrier IPs.</string>
</resources>
